

Sushil Shakya

Date of birth: 09/02/1988 | **Nationality:** Indian | **Gender** Male | (+91) 9821669004 |

sushilshakya75@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/sushil-shakya-513768191/ |

Skype: live:cac3cd30152f1fbe_1

1-C, STREET NO - 6, PRESS ENCLAVE, VIKAS NAGAR, UTTAM NAGAR, 110059, New Delhi,

India

About me: Over the experience of 11 years, I have built a successful career in Operations and Sales & Marketing with the key proficiencies that can make a positive contribution and focusing on operational management and process improvements.

WORK EXPERIENCE

26/10/2018 - CURRENT - Gurugram, India

ASSISTANT MANAGER - SALES & MARKETING - JINDAL ITALIA MARMO I INC.

- · Handle Hard core marketing and client schedule for visits.
- · Coordinate and handle individually meetings with Architects, Interior Designers and Builders.
- · Handle showroom sales of imported marbles and granites.
- Must be able to also I can make Measurement sheets, Invoices and Performa invoice.
- · Use promotional techniques and prepare promotional materials to sell inventory items.
- · Manage digital marketing and promotion;
 - Web Design, SEO, SMO, SMS Marketing,

Promotional activity - Brochure, Greetings, Pamphlets etc.

14/06/2014 - 21/10/2018 - New Delhi, India

ASSISTANT MANAGER - OPERATIONS - CNS WEB TECHNOLOGIES PVT. LTD.

- · Must be able to also Handle Order fulfillment for e-commerce operations.
- Managing Orders from all ecommerce platforms and ensuring all orders are prepared in time.
- · Managing relationship with vendors/partners and handling problem resolution.
- · Manage all aspects of marketing operations, including key personnel.
- Attending all the complaints. Entire Process of Sales order Management Backend Operations
- · Update online products & combos in ecommerce websites with handle all changes in sites.
- Maintaining up to date files of all invoices.

25/11/2010 - 14/04/2014 - New Delhi, India

MIS EXECUTIVE - OPERATIONS - BRINKS GLOBAL INDIA

- · Generating M.I.S. and analyzing business statistics and improving business.
- · Assessment of cash requirement for the ATMs of different bank.
- Attending daily correspondence of the branch relating to ATM operations.
- Collects data for all the ATMs & report to their respective banks.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

05/05/2013 - 15/09/2015 - Meghalaya, India

MBA - SALES & MARKETING - Mahatma Gandhi University

http://www.mgu.edu.in/

https://www.eiilmuniversity.co.in/

07/04/2006 – 25/05/2007 – New Delhi, India HIGHER SECONDARY – CBSE Board Examination

http://web.delhi.gov.in/wps/wcm/connect/DOIT_Education/education/home

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): HINDI PUNJABI

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	B2	C1	B2	C1	B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Microsoft Word | Microsoft Excel | Outlook | Microsoft Powerpoint | Social Media | Instagram | Facebook | Microsoft Office | Skype | Google Drive | Google Docs | LinkedIn | Internet user | Written and Verbal skills | Zoom | Twitter | Presenting | Team-work oriented | Good listener and communicator | Gmail | WhatsApp | Responsibility | Decision-making | Reliability | Motivated | Computer software

I hereby declare that all the information given above is true and correct to the best of my knowledge. All the information shared in the resume is correct, and I take full responsibility for its correctness. I solemnly declare that the information in this resume is true to the best of my knowledge and belief.

New Delhi INDIA



Sushil Shakya